Natalie Moran

London 07476706463 nataliemoran89@live.co.uk natmonlee.github.io/portfolio

Profile

I am a healthcare professional of ten years who has developed a passion for programming. After a career break for travel and study, I am now seeking my first role in software development. I am self-taught and proficient in JavaScript – vanilla, Node, React and basic TypeScript – as well as HTML and CSS including Bootstrap. My personal projects on my website, linked above, include a website that consumes an external API, documentation for my own API design and a browser-based game. I am highly adaptable, dedicated and enthusiastic and have acquired a wide variety of skills through career and travel which I believe would be an asset to any company.

Work History

Self-study June 2022 – Present

- Developing a strong understanding of JavaScript; including promises, asynchronous programming, APIs and working with Node and React
- Writing semantic HTML
- Understanding responsive web design and utilising CSS layout models as well as Bootstrap
- Utilising tools such as VS Code, GitHub and Git Bash terminal
- Currently studying the basics of C#
- Completing online code challenges
- Reading "Eloquent Javascript" by Marjin Haverbeke

Brockwell Park Surgery Care Coordinator (Feb 2021 – June 2022)

November 2019 - June 2022

- Internal promotion after just over a year working at the surgery
- Ran regular searches using the clinical system and exported data to Excel
- Utilised various software to send batch text-messages, refer patients and generate forms and correspondence
- Ensured and tracked appropriate follow-up for patients, focusing particularly on vulnerable groups
- Filed results and documents, adding codes to patient records as required
- Took on additional role as COVID lead during the pandemic, handling all queries, liaising with vaccination centres and organising immunisation of housebound patients
- Assisted in creating work instructions, procedures and training materials
- Contributed to meetings discussing targets and strategies

Receptionist (November 2019 – February 2021)

- The only full-time reception staff member, at times managing independently during the height of the pandemic
- Managed surgery telephone, triaged patients, scheduled appointments, requested prescriptions and registered new patients
- Organised surgery email inbox and handled queries on our website
- Assessed the efficiency of the new website by evaluating its impact on phone and email enquiries.

King's College Hospital Healthcare Assistant

June 2018 – November 2019

- Delivered care to patients on the cardiology ward and intensive care unit
- Provided close supervision to more vulnerable patients when required
- Monitored patient health using hospital equipment and accurately recorded findings on the clinical system
- Maintained enthusiasm and composure during long shifts, challenging work and emergency situations

David Lewis Pharmacy Pharmacy Assistant (April 2015 – January 2018)

July 2012 - January 2018

- Progressed to dispensary after completing relevant qualifications
- Dispensed medication and processed prescriptions on the clinical system
- Accurately filed, counted and recorded prescriptions for monthly submission
- Managed schedule of regular deliveries to patients
- Maintained stock levels and placed monthly bulk orders based on current usage of products

Medicines Counter Assistant (July 2012 - April 2015)

- Operated the till and reconciled cash on a weekly basis
- Independently liaised with suppliers and made decisions on which stock to purchase
- Provided medical advice on topics such as healthy living, smoking cessation and reproductive health

Qualifications

Bath Spa University

September 2007- June 2010

Diploma in English Literature and Creative Writing

Havering Sixth Form College

September 2005 – June 2007

A Levels: English Literature and English Language Combined, Biology, Psychology

AS Level: Mathematics

Hobbies

Include running, scuba diving and PC and board games.